Now we're going, we
're going to see it, we're going to the
intermodular project,
okay?  The other day we were working
with companies in the sector,
okay?   We
were working with the characteristics
of the departments, we
were looking at, let's see, I
don't know if we got to the point of selecting a
project, a product or service.  No,
not yet.
Okay.  Okay.
What do companies need?  Okay,
they need, they may need this.  Okay.
How much is this going to cost me?
What follow-up will I do?  Okay?
And how does this affect
sustainable development?  I have a problem there,
apart from what Pilar will tell you about in
Fall and in Second in Sustainability,
but I have a problem and that is that
artificial intelligence consumes a
lot of processing, it consumes a
lot of electricity.  Okay,
today, today, as we've
already spent a few sessions talking
about
theory, talking about companies,
talking about things that
are obviously on the
agenda and have to be there,
okay?  They are interesting,
but I want to dedicate today's class to
something a little more practical,
which is to explain how the technologies we
are learning will help us
build a project.  In the
end, what we want is to build at
least a dynamic website.  So
to build a dynamic website,
we need to connect
between client and server.  A few
weeks ago, let's see, new document,
a few weeks ago,
right?  And
yes, it should be here,
but oh well.
How odd.
I was creating an SVG.   Wait
a minute
because uh Dam
I'm going to go to
SVG interfaces,
right?  on desktop
SVG
[Music]
because I don't see it right now.
Well, I was making a sort of
outline of the technologies we're going to
work on in this cycle and in this course.
And today's goal is to do a first
exercise in which we begin to look at the
intermodularity part.
Intermodularity means that
subjects and modules must be
connected to each other.
So today we're going to see that we have
a subject called markup languages
and we have a subject,
a professional module actually
called programming.
But of course, how do these modules run
in parallel?  What is the meaning of
these modules?  Well, the idea of
these modules is that we can check
that one module will eventually feed off the
other.  So for that, for that we're going
to see follow-up in the search for
information.  Okay, so here I'm going to create
a new folder called 010 and I'm going to
call it, uh, let's see,
intermodular connection.
Intermular, no,
intermodular.
Here I'm going to make a subfolder
called
basic contents
and I'm going to make a subfolder called 101
exercises.
And I'm going to tell you over the
weeks and months
how the subjects are linked
to each other, but today I'm going to show you how
programming and markup languages ​​are linked
.
There are many ways, but the
simplest one I know is through
a program called Flask, a library
called Flask.
The Flask library first requires
that we have done a pip install flask,
that is, it requires that we have opened a
terminal and that in the terminal we have
put those of you who are on Windows pip
install flask.  If I'm on Linux it's
pip 3 install flask.  And then he'll say
ok, ok, ok.  You now have Flashk
correctly installed.  Okay, first
step,
open a terminal
and install Flask
like this.  That's necessary so that
you can start to function.
Next,
what we're going to do is
002 start flask
and we're going to say that from flask import
flask in uppercase and this is in
lowercase, which means,
but what is Flask?  It's a micro
web server, right?  Flask
is a web microserver
that allows us to generate HTML from
Python.  So, if in programming
we're looking at Python and in
markup languages ​​we're looking at HTML, this is the
piece that will help us, one of the
pieces, but the most important one that
will help us unite the two things.  So
I say application equals flask and I
'm going to put here name- guaj.  You know, I
always tell you that if I put something in
English, it has to be in English,
and if I put something in Spanish, it has to
be in Spanish.  So now I say
app
app punro root.  Later I
will explain that there are routes in a web application
.  Routes are the
different entry points that
an application listens to.  And then we're going
to say deficio
or def root, whatever you want.  That doesn't
matter to me as long as it's in Spanish.  And I
say ration,
I'm going to say root,
sorry, what rout?  Return.
And
this is HTML from Flask.
And finally, now I start the server.
I start the server
and then say, if name is equal to
main.
[Music]
In that case I'm going to say that eh
application dot run
dot run and
debug equals true.  Okay, what does this
mean, let's discuss it line by
line.  First,
I import the Flask library.
Second, I create a new
application.
Now I define what happens in an
initial route.  The route is bar.  The bar is
the base route.  Now you'll see.  And
now I start
the server.
If I run this, now
I'm going to close things around here.  Okay,
this is netbins, okay?  This, what is it?
That's it.  Okay, now I'm going to Dam, I'm
going to first, I'm going to
intermodular project, I'm going to intermodularity.   I
go to exercises and open a
terminal and say, hey, Python 3 003.
Now I start the server and it says, "Don't
worry about the red message,
because it says, it's a
development server."  Okay, yeah, I know.  So,
uh, it says, go into the http/
slash.  Wait,
in http colon slash slash.  Oh.
192 168 or 127
001 5,000.  Okay.  127001
2.5,000.  Port 5,000.   I
enter.  Hey, no.  What happened?  What
happened?  What happened?  It has been closed.
Ah, no, now yes.  I don't know why it was
closed.  Okay, I'm in.  And it says, "This is
HTML from Flask.
And this, guys and girls, is where
the magic begins, right? This is where
the first course of the
DAM cycle really begins, because this is where we're going to
start to see that the subjects
are connected and that they all serve a
purpose. We're going to do more
complex things, okay? So now
next I say 004,
now I print out actual HTML.
Then I come over here and I say,
"Okay, actual HTML has
HTML tags,
okay?  So I create an H1.
So, I come to the server, I stop
Python 3004
and now I reload and I'll see that the text
is no longer text, but it's an HTML H1 heading
,
which means, I'm not saying
that what I'm doing is super
mega clean, okay?  We will see later that this is
not the case.  Today I'm not interested in it being
clean, today I'm interested in it working.
And you'll say, "Yeah, but you taught us
that an HTML file really isn't just
an H1, it should have a series of
basic characteristics, okay? No
problem, effectively, 004 complete HTML.
And instead of doing this, what I'm going to
do is a doc string. It can be done,
okay? It's a little dirty, but it
can be done. And I'm going to put doc type html
html
HTML
head
title
the usual no Hello, Python
and here in the body in the body I'm going to
say,
if you're seeing this it's because
Python is giving it to you.
So now I'll
execute,
stop
Python 3 uh Python 3 h5.
I'll go to the browser,
reload. If you're seeing this it's because
Python is giving it to you. So
Python up until now has been a
really ugly language that allows us to do things. And
HTML is a really cool language that
allows us to make really cool websites, but
those websites don't do anything. Those websites
simply show you the website and that's it.
Those  Websites don't calculate anything. With Flask,
we'll be able to begin to unite the two
worlds. With Flask, we'll be able to create
applications that mix Python with HTML
without any problem. I insist, today I'm
mixing Python with HTML, programming
with markup languages. Later,
we'll continue mixing databases and
also computer environments and systems
. And everything, okay? Because that's why
this is the
intermodular project, because not only do we have to go
through the index planned
by the regional government, which of course we do as well
, but also one of the
objectives of this professional module is to
show you the fit between the different
professional modules, okay? But not
only this, not only this, but 006, I
can also add CSS,
not only can I bring HTML, but I can
come here and I can say style. I create the
style tag
and I tell it something simple, okay? The
paragraph has a red color, that's it.
That simple, minimal CSS. So I
stop. So Python 3 006. I
can also add CSS. I go to the website,
reload, and as we see, we're  putting
CSS, right?
To which you'll say, "Okay, okay, I
see it, I see that I see that Python, I see that
Flask is serving me HTML, but I don't quite
understand why, because in the
end, I'm basically doing the
same thing that I did before with HTML.  Okay?
Okay, right, if you're thinking that, I
understand, but next we're going to
see something we can do with
Flash and HTML, which we can't do
with HTML alone, and that's the following.  007
dynamic content.
And now if I come here and say the
sum is equal to 4 + 3, you see what
nonsense.  I come here now and
say, if you're seeing this, it's because
Python is giving it to you
and the result of the sum,
this is going to seem silly to you, but I
assure you it's not.
And the result
of the addition is eh quote, quote, quote
, more quote, quote, quote,
str to chain chain and sum.
And then
I stop, I
execute.
Oops, I made a mistake when I wrote
Python.   I
execute,
recharge
and the sum result is seven
and that's it.  What did you think?
I thought it was great.
But you will say, eh, this, this,
what is it?  This is a seven.  Which?  I mean,
incredible, indeed.  I mean, what does
this matter?  Instead of going through all
this hassle, I could have just put
the number seven here in HTML, in markup languages,
and that's it.  Okay?  So
what I'm going to do next is, uh, and
yes, Serena, what a mess.  Okay,
so today I don't want to mix too many
subjects at once, I just want to
mix two.
and throughout the weeks we will
mix more subjects.  But what
I want to show you is why this is
important.
So, earlier in language,
sorry, in programming we see the
for structure.  The for structure is
used to repeat something many times.
And if you remember, we did a for day
equals 1, day is less than 31 and day
we increase.  And he would tell us, today is
day one, today is day two, today is day
three, today is day four. We looked at it in a
Python console, right?  This is,
I insist, I am referring to
programming, control structures,
repetition structures, exercises and
the for.  Okay, today is day X of the month and
it came up on the console.  Today is the X day of the
month.  And you would say, well,
fine, but in my life, what good is this
going to do me?  Okay, so now
I'm going to make a calendar
using Python and HTML.  And this is where you're going to
start to understand what
each thing is going to be useful for.  Okay, I'm going to do
this.
I'm going to do the following.  I'm going to say
return string
and here I'm going to say that string
is equal to this.  And here I'm going to say that
gu, that is, quote, quote, quote.  And
string is plus equal to quote, quote,
quote.  Okay, the chain starts here and
continues here.  But now, but now
009.
Now I do a for of days
and I say
and I say,
if I'm in the right place, it seems to me
so.  for day in range from 0 to 31 from 1
to 31
string plus equals good to this same thing to
div class day day
and I'm going to put
a str of day here.
And what is happening?  Well, pay attention.
Because now, as I say, now
the party begins.
Well, what happens is that I
execute
the one we're on, wait a moment
at 009.
Reload.  Attention, I'm going to close this because it's making
me dizzy.   I
reload
and it tells me 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 until the
30th. That is
, in HTML, I have
n't had to create,
you see it here on the right, I haven't had to
manually create each of these dips
because what I've done is unite the
power of
Python's repetition structures with
HTML tags, in this case div class day.  And if
the Python label
repeats it to me, then I repeat it.
But now
the power of CSS comes to our aid
.  Before I do this, before I do
this, by the way, I'm going to say div class
mes
and here div, okay?  and I say div
because if I run it I have a class month
and then within the month I have the days,
okay?  And so it's a little more
organized, but now as I say 010
eh the power of CSS,
okay?  And now I come here and I say
style, style
day is
with, I don't know, 100 pixels, hiked 100
pixels, border, one pixel solid greay and
if I reload it, I think I'll have to
reload the whole thing.  Yes, correct.
I have to reload and Python 3 and 010.
Okay, now I reload and this happens
and each of the days has
become a little square.
Why has it become a little
square?  Because it uses CSS and CSS
calls the elements that have
the class day and gives them a style for
day.
But now next, now
next 011 we use grid, the grid
that I taught you at the beginning of the
afternoon today in markup languages ​​and I will
say
month is display grid
and grid
grid template columns
is auto Auto, auto, auto, auto, auto and
auto.  That is, seven columns, like 7
days in a calendar.
So Python 3011, I
reload the screen
and it shows me and there you have it, a
calendar
and it shows me a calendar,
which means I can then
set the maximum width, right?  I can
give you a moment.  I'm going to put it a
month.  I'm going to put eh with 700 pixels.   It may
be too little.  Now we'll see.
No, it's okay.  Okay, but with this,
I insist, I've made a calendar
mixing
HTML structure,
CSS presentation,
and the power of Python to repeat things
.
And so, as I say, little by little,
over the days we will repeat it.
But I tell you more, I tell you more.  In
programming,
once we made a for loop, we then
started doing some initial nesting
to show you that you couldn't just
make one day, but you could make 12
months.  And then we saw that you could also
do years.
So we're going to do this with
Flask and so I'm going to say 012.
Now I want the whole year.  Let's
assume that every month has 30
days, okay?  And every month starts on
Monday, and later I'll show you
that it's obviously not.  So this over
here,
this over here and I'm going to say string plus
equals and I'm going to say for.
for mes in range from 1 to 13.
Okay, this goes here.
Messing range, this goes here.
Now
this goes here
and this goes here.
Okay,
so for dia in m
I put this here
and if this is correct, if it's indented
correctly,
Python 3 012,
I come here.
Eu, woow, gua.  What happened here?
Okay, wait a minute, something went wrong.  A
second-rate.  What thing?  It looks like a
Tetris calendar.
Okay, month.  Therein lies the problem.  I have not
closed properly.  Let's see.
More equal chain.  More equal chain.  Oh
yeah, sorry.  This goes here.  Now,
now I recharge.
And now, as you can see,
I have the 12 months of a year.  I have the
30 for 12 days.  Okay, you know that
's not correct from that point of
view, okay?  He had effectively created
a ladder.
But what I want to tell you with this, what I
want to tell you with this is that
now, obviously, it's what
Serena was saying, it's a mess.
Indeed, it is a mess.  What I just
did is a demonstration.
By the end of today's class you'll say, "I don't
remember any of the code that was
written and even if I do, it's a
huge mess of code, okay?
Yeah, right. But what I want in this
case is for you to remember the overall concept
of today's class, which is that
subjects can be mixed and should be
mixed and that within the mix of
subjects, each subject is going to
fulfill a function. So, Python is
what's going to calculate things and HTML is what's
going to display things on the
screen.
In this way, with this,
in a few weeks we'll enter
point 002 of selecting a service or
product. And then the question will be,
well, what can you do? What is the
scope of this first course? And above
all, what is the difference between the first
course and the second course? We
also have to be very clear about that,
okay? What is the
intermodular connection? 001 introduction. Mmd.
Now let's move away from the code.
Let's see what the  Subjects,
professional training modules
must have a connection.
First-year students
can create dynamic websites.
Second-year students
can create all kinds of applications.
What can we do in the first year?
In the first year,
markup languages
provide
the ability
to display information to the end user
,
in other words, a website for understanding.
Programming
provides the ability
to add
a layer of calculation underneath,
in other words, a layer of
power, okay?
Databases will
allow us to
store
information persistently.
Development environments will
push us
to create programs that are good. In other
words, programming will allow us to
create programs,
but in development environments, it will make us
ask ourselves if those programs, apart
from working, are well-built,
well-structured, well-developed, and
scale correctly.
Okay? All of that. And finally, computer systems
are the wrapper around everything.
Nothing can be executed
without a computer system.
And this is what we began to see in
today's class, okay?
In today's class,
we began to see
the connection between markup languages
and  Programming. And now,
let's do some more exercises,
okay? Let's see more things. Let's
see, for example, let's see, just a moment.
Well, of course, I want to do this,
but only with things we've seen
so far. In this case, a
for structure, well, obviously, it's
quite useful for us.
Let's see. Programming time,
jump structures,
conditional structures, selection.
Let's see,
look, for example, for example, for
example, a typical, classic, and
characteristic exercise is the creation of a
chess set, okay? Chess, which will later be
useful in second year for the
multimedia and device programming subject
, that is,
game programming. So for that, so for
that, I'm going to try to make a
minimal chess set.
So, new file 013. I create a
punython chess board.
I'll take all this, I'm going to unbundle it.
Strings equal to this,
okay? And I'm left with this. I remove sum 4 +
3, I remove the comments because we already know what
they do,
okay? More than anything, to  Show you that
the basic Flask server is
simpler than it seems. Sandro, let's
create a G3 board in
a game of checkers. Now you'll see. Ah,
now we see.
In first grade, we're going to create a board. In
second grade, in the
multimedia and device programming subject. A subject
of which I have it right here. A subject
of which, out
of five teaching units,
game engines and 2D and 3D game development
are two of the five units, but that,
as I said, is in second grade. Okay, today
what we're going to do is create a
checkers or chess board.
Let's see it. And intermodular connection,
exercises, and let's go. Okay, then
, next, I'll say the
following: How
many cells does an air or checkers board have
? Well, it's 8 by 8, okay? So
and eh cells
declaration
and I say
def board width
equals 8. equals 8, I
meant.
So now next, I'm going to make
a for loop for the,
How would I tell you? For X and another for
Y. Then I say
def
mm
x
in range
of cer to board width
for y in range
of cer board width
that is 8*
And now I say the following.
String here, string there.
And now I say string
plus equal
to div class
and I say I put a C for Zelda.
So if now I execute this,
Python 3
014.
Hey, what happened? I have an error, huh?
Let's see in the fantasero line.
Oops. Ah, def. Oh my God. No, no, no, no.
This is a variable. Okay, I don't know
why I put def there. No, nothing. Out.
Okay, I reload and I have no more and no less
than 64 cells. 8* 8 64 cells. But
of course, now
you obviously see, I have 64 cells there, so I have to
give them a little style like a
chessboard shape, so
015,
a little CSS, although not very legal.
So, here I say  style,
style and I say Zelda, the element that
has the Zelda class, okay? The
Zelda class is with, I don't know, 50 pixels. Hiked,
50 pixels. Let's see what happens. And
now I
reload
015.
Reload.
Oh, yeah, sorry. And a solid one pixel border
. Uh, Grey,
okay? And the result is this. I have a
series of cells,
okay? But now, but now once I
have cells, well I
want to tell it that now 016 grid in the body, so body is display grid and grid template columns is auto and auto multiplied by 8 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8. That is, a chessboard has eight columns, so grid in the body.
Python 3016.
Reload. Okay. And now I have a body
that has 8 * 8 16. I have there the
chessboard or checkers or whatever
you want.
But of course, now a little bit to focus,
get the end of this exercise on track.
Of course, I know that in chess or
checkers, cells go like white, black,
white, black, white, black. Okay?
So, like this, like this,
now let's see it next.
I'm going to say
if
y
divided by 2 equals 0, the
integer remainder of the division.
In this case, conditional structure 017
conditional
els
otherwise,
string equals this and cell cell
equals black. A black cell.
What is a black cell? A black
cell is a cell whose
background is black.
Let's see how this turned out.
Python 3 017. Pay attention to what I'm telling you,
right? It's a drawing, but I put in a
conditional. If an expression is true,
we're going to do one thing, but if it's not
true, we're going to do another. Okay? So I
come over here, I'm executing, I
reload. Mm, almost, almost. What happened?
What happened is that it gave me the
same rule for all the rows, but
of course, we know that in the  odd rows there
is one rule and in the even rows
the opposite rule is present. So, once
again, this transferred logic has a
different rule
in each row.
I say if
x divided by x divided by 2 equals
0,
in that case something is going to happen.
And if not,
something else is going to happen.
This one is black and this one isn't. In other
words, I'm inverting the logic. Just a
moment, now I'll add comments to
finish this part of the class. Before
that,
Python 3 018
and reload. And now I do have the
chess or checkers board or whatever
you want created. And
Python has helped me create that board, because
if I had to do it,
if I had to do it in HTML, I
could die of boredom here writing
the cells one by one and getting them right, but you do
n't have to do that because
that's simply what we have HTML for, to
present beautifully on the screen what we
want to present and Python to
calculate what we want to present.
Okay? And now, having said that,
let's add comments to the
exercise.
Okay. And for that, I'm going to  to do the
following. First of all,
of course, this is a string, I can't do it here.
Okay,
first of all, let's start with a
CSS style. I'm going to do one thing. Instead of
putting the comments there, which will make the
code more complicated later, I'm going to put them
here.
Now I
define the width of the board and
first I go through
the cells in X.
Then I go through
the cells in Y. Okay, the cells in X
are horizontal, the cells in Y are
vertical.
And then I say,
if we're in an even row,
in that case,
if we're
in an
even column, do this. And if not,
if we're in an
odd column.
Now
if we're in an
odd row, odd. And this is if we're in an even
column.
And this is if we're in an
odd column.
I hope I don't get a
comment error, okay? A
comment line error. Let's see it.
And Python 3,
uh,
019.
Okay, correct. Okay, it's the same, the
result will be the same. The only thing
that happens is that now the code has
comments in Python so that  You can
better understand what it does, okay? And
this is what we're going to do in this
subject. There will be sessions in which
we'll talk about theory, business,
market research, business models,
all of that. And there will be other days in
which we'll be working with code with
the goal of showing you that the code we
're learning can be used to
build applications. At this
point,
uh, this is where I start to tell you that
if programming is one and
markup language is one, an intermodular project
isn't 1 + 1, it's ig 2. An intermodular project
is 1 + 1. Combining
those two components, you can do a
lot more things than you could
with the more separate components.
And then adding databases, we'll see
that 1 + 1 + 1 isn't three, it's 100. With
databases, you'll see that programming,
markup languages, and databases
begin to multiply each other, and you'll see
that we can create really
brutal projects, okay? So, this is the
objective, obviously one of the
main objectives of the
intermodular project subject.
Now, now throughout the weeks,
as you analyze the
business model you want to work with,
on the one hand, you'll ask me.
Of course, Serena, you
asked me a few days ago about
the clothing store, okay? A fashion store,
uh, online, as you can imagine,
where today we're seeing
chess squares, well, later on, what we'll
do is load products from a
database and instead of painting them like
chess cells, we'll paint them
like products from a clothing store,
okay? So, each one is about
you thinking about what you
want to do and little by little,
over the weeks. We haven't
finished yet, not even in September. Today
is the last day of September of classes
with me, but before the end of September,
we're already starting to mix pieces,
so we have the whole course
ahead of us to teach you how to mix
the pieces and all that, okay? And well,
I want to end today's class
by telling you what  Next.
Indicating the following. As I
mentioned at the beginning of the
class, uh, you're now starting to see
evaluations, okay? With which you're now
starting to see both new exercises
and results, as ok, in
principle everyone should start to
have uh their content. Uh, I have to
regenerate some exercises, okay? With
which I'll modify this because
the text is added there, but anyway, I'm
working a little bit every day. So if
we go, for example, to programming, you'll
see that now instead of seeing a
drop-down menu, you'll see the
following happen. What we're seeing
here is an exercise completed and
evaluated.
What we see here is an exercise
not yet completed. The icon on the
page is not completed. And you'll see that from
time to time Yes. Ah, yes, yes, the
eye. Nothing, it's just silly. It's a bit
of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I'll
tell you more about it later, but it was a bit of
the eye. It looks like the girl's eye in
this Korean series,
Squid Game.  Okay? The little girl who watches you to
see if you move or not. So it's like
an eye watching you while you take a
test. It's a lie, it's JavaScript. Okay,
if it's scary, it's exactly what I
wanted. Indeed, that was the
objective, okay? And uh, the idea is that,
if you see that it's a blank page, it
's a task you haven't done
yet. Okay, 2010 eyes. I don't know what
2010 eyes are, tell us, because
the 2010 movie Odyssey 2 came to mind
, but it must not be that
because I don't remember any eyes in that movie,
but well, I don't know. Okay. And if
ever, well, when you do an activity
on web pages, ah, to make them
more alive, yes, that's a bit
the same. Indeed, it's a
small widget with JavaScript that
moves with the mouse, but it doesn't do anything
else. It's like an animation, so,
yes, it's more or less the same  Same. Yes. Okay. And
if you ever see that you finish
an exercise, okay? And when you finish the
exercise, you see an hourglass appear
. The hourglass means
that the system recognizes that you have
finished that exercise and have
sent it for evaluation, but it has not yet been
evaluated, okay? So I
calculate that once every 24
hours I will go through the evaluation process,
but I don't know. Okay, I say this because, for
example, in this case we can see that
Serena has left a constants file here
, okay? An activity,
but uh, it has not been evaluated yet because
you remember that at the beginning of the afternoon
I downloaded it. So
next what I'll do here, I'm going to
close this, what I'll do here
tonight, okay?, is enter. I say
tonight because when I evaluate
artificial intelligence it
crashes my computer, what I usually try to do
is start it when I'm not
there. So I'll go to Eval. Inside
useful I
have a Python script here.  called
evalua, so I'm not going to run it
now because it will break my computer
, but what evalua does is it
corrects the exercises that I have
pending to correct and then
synchronize. What it does is that the
evaluations that I have generated are
uploaded to the server, okay? So,
as I said, that is planned to be
done,
well I told you, once every 24 hours, once
every 48 hours, I don't know, but what I
want to tell you is that from
here on, well in the next few days we will
talk, starting little by little,
okay? Starting to build
exercises and that's it. Meanwhile,
meanwhile locally,
locally I have
a control panel here, it
's only locally, where it
tells me, it
tells me what you are submitting. It
also notifies me of which ones are
pending to be corrected. It tells me
who is submitting, what grades they are
getting, which people have not submitted
yet and so on, okay? So,
the idea is that on the one hand I
can keep track of you from
the  Beginning, early follow-up.
Each of you should also receive
feedback as quickly as possible on what you're
doing, whether it's good or
bad, and what you can do to
improve it and all that. Remember what I
mentioned last week in the
email: the laxity parameter is at
zero, okay? That means that
right now, in the first few weeks, the
artificial intelligence is helping you, okay? It
raises your grade, it gives you a little help—I
mean, it's not like next month it's
going to go from 0 to 10, okay? In
October, maybe I'll raise it to one, and then
in November I'll raise it to two, okay? And
so, the more the course progresses,
the stricter—without going overboard,
obviously—but the stricter the
artificial intelligence will be when it comes to
grading. And as I always say,
I'm always going to be on top of the
artificial intelligence to make sure
that, as far as possible, it doesn't
tell you nonsense, doesn't suggest
impossible things, it evaluates you fairly, and so on.
Okay. Okay, well, we'll take a 10-
minute break, and then we'll get on with the
computer systems class, the second part of
this afternoon, okay? And with that, we
'll have finished
this afternoon's classes.